# Stephen Bunel

I am an entry level IT Technician 1 with no IT work experience but I have a passion for IT. I have done all the things IT nerds did such as installing 10+ different versions Of Linux etc.. <a href="IMPORTANT!">IMPORTANT!</a> Visit <a href="Stephenbunel.com">stephenbunel.com</a> to get a better picture of what I am capable of and what I can bring to your company.

Website - stephenbunel.com (785) 414-0474 steve@stephenbunel.com

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Guardian Electric, Saint Marys KS - Electrician

MONTH 2019 - PRESENT. A mix of Full-time/Part-time

Working primarily as an electrician I also helped with some technical issues such as setting up a new business email and fixing their computers.

# Contracting work for KG Moats & Sons still working for Guardian Electric , St. Marys KS - Electrician

April 2021 - May 2021 + some acational work here and there on weekends

I was hired as a helper/electrician and sent out to Kansas City to work at a new U-Haul fulfillment center. My primary duty was to assist their electricians/engineers while they were wiring up and programming a massive new conveyor system.

## **Online Ecommerce Business** - Digital Entrepreneur

April 2020 - May 2021. Paused - focusing 100% of my time on developing my IT skills.

Through applied business knowledge and technical skills, I generated thousands of \$\$\$ in ecommerce sales through shopify and amazon FBA. I also have experience with google ads, amazon PPC and SEO optimization.

### **EDUCATION**

Saint Mary's Academy in KS, Penn Foster + Self-Taught IT PRO

### **SKILLS**

3+ years of personal experience working with various aspects of computers from Web Dev to building PC's to configuring business email. Basic knowledge of Active Directory + some other business software.

A+ 2001 passed. On track to be fully certified very soon. Then going to get my NET+ and SEC+, continuously advancing my technical skills to keep up to date with the latest technologies.

HTML & CSS + Git + dabbled with the major programming languages such as python, javascript. I also have deep knowledge of ecommerce and web services such as Shopify, Wix etc.. To get more info about my skill sets visit stephenbunel.com

